(this.webpackJsonptreasure_trails=this.webpackJsonptreasure_trails||[]).push([[0],{30:function(e){e.exports=JSON.parse('[{"question":"A Pure Glow","answer":"Paul Gower","location":"Before Gower Quest, at the Gower Farm. After, at the Life Altar.","challenge":"N/A"},{"question":"A Zen She","answer":"Zenesha","location":"East Ardougne\'s center square, in the platebody shop along its southern side.","challenge":"Puzzle Box"},{"question":"Ace Match Elm","answer":"Cam the Camel","location":"North of Al Kharid, west of the Duel Arena.  No Camulet is needed to speak with the camel.","challenge":"Puzzle Box"},{"question":"Ah; wet arm","answer":"Amaethwr","location":"Lletya\'s farming patch.","challenge":"Lockbox"},{"question":"Aha Jar","answer":"Jaraah","location":"Al Kharid, Duel Arena\'s hospital/entrance.","challenge":"N/A"},{"question":"An Paint Tonic","answer":"Captain Ninto","location":"Under White Wolf Mountain, in the bar. Requires the Fishing Contest quest.","challenge":"Puzzle Box"},{"question":"Arc O Line","answer":"Caroline","location":"North Witchaven, next to the rowboat. After the Sea Slug quest, wanders the coast. After the Kennith\'s Concerns quest, found upstairs in her house directly west of the church.","challenge":"11 (0 after Salt in the Wound)"},{"question":"Are Col","answer":"Oracle","location":"Ice Mountain\'s northern peak, west of Edgeville.","challenge":"48"},{"question":"Arr! So I am a crust, and?","answer":"Ramara du Croissant","location":"Piscatoris Fishing Colony\'s furnace room; requires the Swan Song quest.","challenge":"Puzzle Box"},{"question":"Bail Trims","answer":"Brimstail","location":"Tree Gnome Stronghold, in the cave west of the southern bank.","challenge":"N/A"},{"question":"By Look","answer":"Bolkoy","location":"Tree Gnone Village\'s general store, up a ladder.","challenge":"13"},{"question":"Boast B","answer":"Sabbot","location":"Burthorpe, in the dungeon to the north of the Warriors\' Guild.  After the Death Plateau quest, he is in the chamber to the west.","challenge":"N/A"},{"question":"C On Game Hoc","answer":"Gnome Coach","location":"West of the Grand Tree in Tree Gnome Stronghold, walking around outside the Gnome Ball course.","challenge":"6"},{"question":"Dt Run B","answer":"Brundt","location":"Relleka\'s Longhall, in the center of town.","challenge":"4"},{"question":"Eek Zero Op","answer":"Zookeeper","location":"Ardougne Zoo","challenge":"40, +1 after Eagles\' Peak, +1 after Hunt for Red Raktuber"},{"question":"El Ow","answer":"Lowe","location":"Varrock\'s archery store","challenge":"N/A"},{"question":"Ergo I Dig Clay","answer":"Celia Diggory","location":"Varrock\'s digsite, just outside of the Empty Throne Room.","challenge":"Tower Puzzle"},{"question":"Err Cure It","answer":"Recruiter","location":"West Ardougne\'s center square.","challenge":"20"},{"question":"Goblin Kern","answer":"King Bolren","location":"Tree Gnome Village, next to the spirit tree.","challenge":"N/A"},{"question":"Got A Boy","answer":"Gabooty","location":"Tai Bwo Wannai\'s center.","challenge":"11"},{"question":"Gulag Run","answer":"Uglug Nar","location":"Just west of Jiggig, which is south of Castle Wars and East of Gu\'Tanoth.","challenge":"Puzzle Box"},{"question":"Halt Us","answer":"Luthas","location":"Musa Point, Karamja, the hut east of the banana plantation on .","challenge":"33 (or None)"},{"question":"Hated","answer":"Death","location":"Death\'s office; touch the hourglass just north of Draynor\'s lodestone.","challenge":"N/A"},{"question":"He Do Pose. It Is Cultrrl, Mk?","answer":"Riki the Sculptor\'s model","location":"East Keldagrim, inside of the gravestone shop.","challenge":"Puzzle Box"},{"question":"Hear A Lady Rant","answer":"Lady Trahaearn","location":"Prifddinas, by the Seren stones in the Trahaearn District.","challenge":"N/A"},{"question":"Icy Fe","answer":"Fycie","location":"Rantz\'s cave, south-east of Gu\'Tanoth.","challenge":"N/A"},{"question":"I Eat Its Chart Hints Do U","answer":"Shiratti the Cusstodian","location":"Nardah, in the building north of the fountain.","challenge":"Puzzle Box"},{"question":"I Faffy Run","answer":"Fairy Nuff","location":"Before the quest A Fairy Tale II and after A Fairy Tale III: just north of the bank in Zanaris. Between A Fairy Tale II & III: get the certificate from the potion shelf in her house north of the bank, then use the fairy ring codes: air, dir, djq, ajs.","challenge":"Puzzle Box"},{"question":"Im Krom","answer":"Rommik","location":"Rimmington, in the general store.","challenge":"7"},{"question":"I SAW THE LIE","answer":"Ali the Wise","location":"Nardah, in the northernmost house.","challenge":"N/A"},{"question":"Iz A Ammo Load for Mrs Yakkers","answer":"Moldark, Emissary of Zamorak","location":"Edgeville, north-east of the bank.","challenge":"7 (3 after the quest Ritual of the Mahjarrat, but before Rebuilding Edgeville)"},{"question":"Land Doomd","answer":"Odd Old Man","location":"The limestone mine west of Paterdomus, east of Varrock, and north of the Digsite.","challenge":"Puzzle Box"},{"question":"Lark In Dog","answer":"King Roald","location":"Varrock Palace, in the south-eastern section on the ground floor.","challenge":"24"},{"question":"Me Am The Calc","answer":"Cam the Camel","location":"North of Al Kharid, west of the Duel Arena.  No Camulet is needed to speak with the camel.","challenge":"Puzzle Box"},{"question":"Me if","answer":"Femi","location":"Tree Gnome Stronghold, just outside of the gates.","challenge":"N/A"},{"question":"Nod med","answer":"Edmond","location":"East Ardougne, behind the north-westernmost house.","challenge":"3"},{"question":"O Birdz A Zany En Pc","answer":"Cap\'n Izzy no Beard","location":"Brimhaven, at the entrance to the agility arena.","challenge":"33"},{"question":"O eastern wishes","answer":"Sensei Seaworth","location":"Tuai Leit, the south-western section of the center.","challenge":"Towers Puzzle"},{"question":"Ok Co","answer":"Cook","location":"Lumbridge Castle, in the kitchen on the ground floor.","challenge":"7"},{"question":"Or A Vile","answer":"Valerio","location":"Al Kharid, next to the dancers south-west of Citharede Abbey.","challenge":"17"},{"question":"Or Zinc Fumes Ward","answer":"Wizard Frumscone","location":"Yanille, basement of the Wizard\'s Guild.  Boostable 66 Magic to enter.","challenge":"Puzzle Box"},{"question":"Pin heir all in place","answer":"Philipe Carnillean","location":"Before the quest Carnillean Rising, in the Carnillean household in south-western East Ardougne.  After the quest, depends on Quest Points: [400+: TzHaar Fight Caves]. [350+: Piscatoris Fishing Colony\'s machine room]. [300+: Oldak\'s house in northwest Dorgesh-Kaan]. [250+: very bottom of Polypore Dungeon]. [200+: The Green Ghost Inn in Port Phasmatys]. [150+: Shilo Village, top floor of Paramaya\'s Inn]. [100+: Mountain Camp in the Fremennik Province]. [50+: Inside Ardougne\'s Combat Training Camp].","challenge":"N/A"},{"question":"Peaty Pert","answer":"Party Pete","location":"North-eastern Falador, in the Party Room.","challenge":"N/A"},{"question":"Profs Lose Wrong Pie","answer":"Professor Onglewip","location":"South of Draynor, on the ground floor of the Wizards\' Tower.","challenge":"Puzzle Box"},{"question":"R Ak Mi","answer":"Karim","location":"Al Kharid, Kebab shop south of the furnace.","challenge":"5"},{"question":"Rebirth Not Ritually","answer":"Brother Tranquility","location":"Mos Le\'Harmless docks or Harmony Island (during and after The Great Brain Robbery).","challenge":"N/A"},{"question":"Red Art Tans","answer":"Trader Stan","location":"The southern Port Sarim docks, next to the charter ship.","challenge":"Puzzle Box"},{"question":"Reign us if immortal","answer":"Malignius Mortifier","location":"South-east of the clan camp and north-west of Port Sarim, surrounded by elemental mages.","challenge":"Lockbox"},{"question":"Sequin Dirge","answer":"Queen Sigrid","location":"If the quest Blood Runs Deep is completed, in the Miscellania Castle throne room.  Otherwise, in the throne room of Etceteria Castle.","challenge":"Puzzle Box"},{"question":"Snah","answer":"Hans","location":"Outside of Lumbridge Castle (walks around the castle clockwise)","challenge":"N/A"},{"question":"Soy Drain","answer":"Ysondria","location":"Lumbridge Swamp, at the Nexus.","challenge":"8"},{"question":"Stab Ob","answer":"Sabbot","location":"Burthorpe, in the dungeon to the north of the Warriors\' Guild.  After the Death Plateau quest, he is in the chamber to the west.","challenge":"N/A"},{"question":"Taboo Rises Shyly","answer":"Soothsayer Sybil","location":"In The Heart of Gielinor (south-west of Nardah), outside of the entrance to Telos.","challenge":"N/A"},{"question":"Them Cal Came","answer":"Cam the Camel","location":"North of Al Kharid, west of the Duel Arena.  No Camulet is needed to speak with the camel.","challenge":"Puzzle Box"},{"question":"We Irk Over Namesake","answer":"Ramokee Skinweaver","location":"Polypore Dungeon, at the bottom.","challenge":"N/A"},{"question":"Winsome Lad","answer":"Wise Old Man","location":"Draynor Village, in the house just north of the bank.","challenge":"N/A"},{"question":"Winston Lane","answer":"Nials Newton","location":"Taverley, next to the lodestone.","challenge":"10"}]')},32:function(e,t,a){e.exports=a(48)},37:function(e,t,a){},42:function(e,t,a){},47:function(e,t,a){},48:function(e,t,a){"use strict";a.r(t);var n=a(0),o=a.n(n),r=a(27),l=a.n(r),s=(a(37),a(10)),i=a(11),c=a(13),h=a(12),u=a(14),m=a(3),d=function(e){function t(){return Object(s.a)(this,t),Object(c.a)(this,Object(h.a)(t).apply(this,arguments))}return Object(u.a)(t,e),Object(i.a)(t,[{key:"render",value:function(){return o.a.createElement(o.a.Fragment,null,o.a.createElement("div",{className:"main-design",style:{backgroundColor:"#172136"}},o.a.createElement(m.b,{className:"main-menu-options",to:"/treasure-trails-helper/anagrams"},o.a.createElement("p",null,"Anagrams")),o.a.createElement(m.b,{className:"main-menu-options",to:"/treasure-trails-helper/challenges"},o.a.createElement("p",null,"Challenges")),o.a.createElement(m.b,{className:"main-menu-options",to:"/treasure-trails-helper/coordinates"},o.a.createElement("p",null,"Coordinates")),o.a.createElement(m.b,{className:"main-menu-options",to:"/treasure-trails-helper/cryptics"},o.a.createElement("p",null,"Cryptics")),o.a.createElement(m.b,{className:"main-menu-options",to:"/treasure-trails-helper/lockboxes"},o.a.createElement("p",null,"Lockboxes")),o.a.createElement(m.b,{className:"main-menu-options",to:"/treasure-trails-helper/maps"},o.a.createElement("p",null,"Maps")),o.a.createElement(m.b,{className:"main-menu-options",to:"/treasure-trails-helper/puzzleboxguide"},o.a.createElement("p",null,"Puzzle Box Guide")),o.a.createElement(m.b,{className:"main-menu-options",to:"/treasure-trails-helper/scans"},o.a.createElement("p",null,"Scans")),o.a.createElement(m.b,{className:"main-menu-options",to:"/treasure-trails-helper/skillingriddles"},o.a.createElement("p",null,"Skilling Riddles")),o.a.createElement("span",{id:"btn-to-top"})))}}]),t}(n.Component),g=(a(42),a(22)),f=a(24),w=a(30),p=a(15),b=a(5),E=function(e){function t(){var e,a;Object(s.a)(this,t);for(var n=arguments.length,o=new Array(n),r=0;r<n;r++)o[r]=arguments[r];return(a=Object(c.a)(this,(e=Object(h.a)(t)).call.apply(e,[this].concat(o)))).state={query:""},a.handleQueryChange=function(){a.setState({query:a.search.value})},a}return Object(u.a)(t,e),Object(i.a)(t,[{key:"formPreventDefault",value:function(e){e.preventDefault()}},{key:"render",value:function(){var e=this;return window.onscroll=function(){!function(){var e=window.location.origin;"http://localhost:3000"!==e&&"https://tmh6395.github.io"!==e||(document.body.scrollTop>20||document.documentElement.scrollTop>20?document.getElementById("btn-to-top").style.display="block":document.getElementById("btn-to-top").style.display="none")}()},o.a.createElement(o.a.Fragment,null,o.a.createElement("form",{id:"search-form",onSubmit:this.formPreventDefault},o.a.createElement(p.a,null,o.a.createElement(b.a,{xs:1}),o.a.createElement(b.a,{xs:1},o.a.createElement("button",{id:"btn-to-home"},o.a.createElement(m.b,{to:"/treasure-trails-helper",id:"link-to-home"},o.a.createElement(g.a,{icon:f.a})))),o.a.createElement(b.a,{xs:7}),o.a.createElement(b.a,{style:{alignSelf:"center"}},o.a.createElement("input",{id:"search-bar",placeholder:"Search",ref:function(t){return e.search=t},onChange:this.handleQueryChange,autoFocus:!0})))),o.a.createElement("div",null,o.a.createElement(p.a,null,o.a.createElement(b.a,null),o.a.createElement(b.a,{xs:7,id:"result-container"},w.map((function(t,a){if(t.question.toLowerCase().includes(e.state.query.toLowerCase()))return o.a.createElement("div",{className:"results",key:a},o.a.createElement("h1",null,o.a.createElement("span",null,"Anagrams:")," ",t.question),o.a.createElement("p",null,o.a.createElement("span",null,"Solution:")," ",t.answer),o.a.createElement("p",null,o.a.createElement("span",null,"Location:")," ",t.location),o.a.createElement("p",null,o.a.createElement("span",null,"Challenge (if applicable):")," ",t.challenge))}))),o.a.createElement(b.a,null))),o.a.createElement("div",null,o.a.createElement(p.a,null,o.a.createElement(b.a,{xs:1}),o.a.createElement(b.a,{xs:1},o.a.createElement("button",{id:"btn-to-top"},o.a.createElement(m.b,{to:"#",id:"link-to-top",onClick:function(){return window.scrollTo(0,0)}},o.a.createElement(g.a,{icon:f.b})))))))}}]),t}(n.Component),q=a(9),y=(a(46),a(47),function(e){function t(){return Object(s.a)(this,t),Object(c.a)(this,Object(h.a)(t).apply(this,arguments))}return Object(u.a)(t,e),Object(i.a)(t,[{key:"render",value:function(){return o.a.createElement(m.a,null,o.a.createElement(p.a,{id:"main-row"},o.a.createElement(b.a,null,o.a.createElement(q.c,null,o.a.createElement(q.a,{exact:!0,path:"/treasure-trails-helper",component:d}),o.a.createElement(q.a,{exact:!0,path:"/treasure-trails-helper/anagrams",component:E})," */}"))))}}]),t}(n.Component));Boolean("localhost"===window.location.hostname||"[::1]"===window.location.hostname||window.location.hostname.match(/^127(?:\.(?:25[0-5]|2[0-4][0-9]|[01]?[0-9][0-9]?)){3}$/));l.a.render(o.a.createElement(y,null),document.getElementById("root")),"serviceWorker"in navigator&&navigator.serviceWorker.ready.then((function(e){e.unregister()}))}},[[32,1,2]]]);
//# sourceMappingURL=main.b0b07012.chunk.js.map